Meet Syed Muhammad Shuja Haider
...Or as he goes by his other aliases:
YourHit, Shuja or Shuja-HaiderDEV.
He has a story of lies, unmet promises and vaporware
He started off like any software developer, projects here and there, nothing special.
In the month of October in 2022 Shuja would start a project
...that would aim to reshape modding of blackberry devices entirely.
He would name this project HaxBerry.
HæxBerry was just like any other software project and quite quickly people caught wind of it
Around this time, people desperate for another way to hack their blackberries decided to help.
...what they thought was a developer in need of more hardware, and so they sent devices after devices to him, expecting exploits back.
Trusting him was one of their biggest mistakes.
Shuja had already started making promises and at this point,
had broken every. single. one. of. them.
Eventually, the devices he had lied to obtain for free had arrived.
And a group of absolutely ripped open-source professionals decided to
...press on for details on the progress of his project.
This obviously made him quite uneasy, so he tried everything to distract them,
From personal attacks to other distraction techniques.
Obviously, they saw straight through his shit and he finally cracked,
giving us a date.
That date is today, and theres still absolutely no source code or update on HæxBerry.
With no source or release or even S*uja, the community felt betrayed.
He delivered promises but never delivered a product, taking others devices with him as well.
Avoid S*uja.
He is not a person to be trusted.
Subtitles made by PEPSIMANTR/Candela.
Happy Mother's day.
We <3 Alyssa!
* Some very nice words to Shuja. *